本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕組 原創翻譯製作
深影字幕組論壇地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻譯： 阿休休 易如反掌 Mstower 白雲喵喵
校對&後期： 阿休休
妖女迷行 第三季第三集
坎耶·歐馬立·韋斯特 美國說唱歌手
星球大戰反派 天行者阿納金黑化後改名為達斯·維達
雙關：勃起
溫迪·懷內嘉賓
有些人就是沒法接受"不行"這個回答
Some guys just can't take "No" For an answer.
莫瑞根命令要回那張照片!
The Morrigan wants that photo!
哦 這事我還真不能怪她 你看了沒?
Oh, I can't blame her. Have you seen it?
不太雅觀啊!
Awkward!
肯吉助攻!得分!
Kenzi for the assist! Yes!
你覺得那招如何? 我假裝摔倒
Did you like that part? Where I pretended to fall on my ass
但其實像顆隱形導彈一樣正中目標
when actually I was like a stealth missile lasering in on target.
幹得好 記得提醒我幫你報名"與異種共舞"
Smooth. Remind me to book you on "Dancing With The Fae".
有那種玩意兒?
Is that a thing?
少說話多做事 快幫我把這高丑黑拽走 好嗎?
Just help me drag tall, dark and hideous out of sight, okay?
你懂得 要成為溫迪·懷內我還欠火候
You know, far be it from me to be a Wendy Whiner...
毫無懸念
Totally.
但這是本周第三次混球異種來襲了
But this is the third Faebag attack this week.
你什麼意思 溫迪?
Your point, Wendy?
昨天是一個長的像裡吉斯的雙頭怪
Yesterday it was the two-headed thingie that looked like Regis.
那之前是個賣熱狗的小販
Then before that it was that hotdog vendor
但其實是個噴火的...?
that turned out to be a fire- breathing...?
- 要我說應該是 青蛙? - 海蜇?
- I wanna say, frog? - Jellyfish?
管它是什麼 我們海扁了它一頓
Whatever it was, we kicked its gelatinous ass.
我從未想過我會這麼說 但我就是個人類 波
You know, I never thought I'd say this, but I'm only human, Bo.
無意冒犯 遇上這事你也不怎麼歡樂啊
And, no offense, but you ain't lookin' so chipper either.
無論莫瑞根派來什麼異種 我都應付得了
Hey, whatever the Morrigan dishes out, I can handle it.
昨天那記鐵拳打得你還頭暈否?
You still got that doozie from yesterday's slug fest?
昨天那是刀傷
Yesterday it was a cut.
今天是淤青 我在癒合中
Today it is a bruise. I'm healing.
- 慢慢地 要很慢地 - 你說什麼呢?
- Slowly. Very slowly. - What are you saying?
那個醫生...我意思是...
The doc... I mean...
像不像是用倉鼠滾輪
you know, isn't it like trying to charge an iPad
- 試著給Ipad充電? - 好吧 暫停一下
- with a hamster wheel? - Okay, time out.
你到底哪兒不待見勞倫?
What exactly do you have against Lauren?
啥?
Moi?
得了 肯吉
Oh, come on, Kenzi, with
你那些個挖苦加翻白眼
the little digs and the rolling of the eyes...
- 我又不傻 - 呃...
- I'm not stupid. - Well...
這可是機會 趁我還撐得住
Here's your chance, while I'm still high
不想吸元療傷之時 發洩出來吧
off my wicked moves. Get it out of your system!
她愛指手畫腳 佔有慾強 控制欲強
She is bossy, territorial, and controlling.
她覺得你幼稚 不負責任 還粘人
She thinks you're immature, irresponsible and clingy.
你這麼說!?
She does!?
你自己都那麼說過自己
Oh, you've said those things about yourself.
是啊 但是自己說自己那叫可愛好嗎
Yeah, but when I say it, it is adorable.
好吧 關鍵是我愛勞倫
Okay, the point is I love Lauren.
她對我很重要 你也是
She's a huge part of my life. As are you.
所以這場"閨蜜"對戰"女友"的戲碼
So in the Battle of BFF versus Main Squeeze,
我們該叫停了 明白嗎?
I think it's time we called a truce. Got it?
現在 大家和波一條心 去喝酒吧 我請客
Now, all those on Team Bo... drinks are on me.
那才對...
That's right...
布魯斯...你真讓我失望
Oh, Bruce... you disappoint me.
- 我叫斯蒂夫 - 怎麼回事呢?
- I'm Steve... - How did this happen?
不是我的錯 她有個後援
It's not my fault, she had an army.
- 別侮辱我的智商!
- Don't insult my intelligence!
你撒謊功力比你哥哥埃裡克都差
You're a worse liar than your brother, Eric.
- 他叫戴夫 - 我才不管!
- Dave. - I don't care!
要不是我剛去做了美甲
If I hadn't just had my nails done,
我早就親手把你的心挖出來了
I'd rip your beating heart out myself.
您真是太善良了
You're too kind.
我覺得某人的氣焰
I think someone's getting
真是越來越囂張了
a little too big for her leather britches.
快了 我的乖乖...快了
Soon, my pet... soon.
如果我們的小淫妖覺得玩得起
If Li'l Bo Bleep thinks she can play in the big leagues...
那就讓遊戲開始吧
let the games begin.
當你不知道你是誰時 生活會很艱辛
Life is hard when you don't know who you are.
當你知道真相後 生活會更艱難
It's harder when you don't know what you are.
我的愛伴隨死神的降臨
My love carries a death sentence.
我迷失了多年 在藏匿中找尋
I was lost for years, searching while hiding.
那個不為人知的屬於我的世界
Only to find that I belonged to a world hidden from humans.
但我已經厭倦了躲藏
I won't hide anymore.
我要過自己想要的生活
I will live the life I choose.
心電圖 核磁共振 植物病毒檢查
Ekg, mri, emv...
讀到虐戀劇情的時候再叫我
Wake me up when you get to S&M.
看吧 事實上 伐克斯...
See, the truth of it, Vex, is that...
別 別忽悠我 醫生 有話直說吧
No, don't sugar coat it, Doc. Just give it to me straight.
好吧 生理學上看 你的胳膊已經痊癒了
Okay... there is nothing physically wrong with your arm,
而且神經系統 肌肉骨系統也沒什麼問題...
or your nervous system, or your musculoskeletal system...
那 為什麼 我不能
Then... why... can't I...
- 使用異種能力? - 你還真會定期爆點
- Get it up? - Oh, regular riot, you are.
既然沒有生理學上的理論
Since there's no physiological
來解釋你的催眠術為什麼無效
reason for your mesmeric impotence...
啊哈!我讓你撓癢癢了!
Aha! I made you do that!
- 沒 其實 剛剛只是有點癢 - 該死的!
- No, actually, that was just an itch. - Damn you!
我意思是你的"情況"
What I'm trying to say is that your "Condition"
可能實際是心理問題
may be psychological in nature.
你意思是我廢了?
What, you sayin' I'm whacked?
像個瘋子似的? 傻子缺八兩?
Like I'm a nutter? A few ounces short of a pound?
以你的年紀 這現象很常見
It's not at all uncommon in Fae your age.
你知道你在跟誰說話嗎?
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?
讓你感受一下伐克斯之怒!
You shall feel the wrath of Vex!
擦
Bah!
你怎麼還沒勒死自己?!
Why aren't you strangling yourself by now?!
沒什麼好尷尬的
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
其實我有本小冊子...
I actually have the pamphlet...
哦 省省你那套可悲的醫生對病人態度
Oh, save your pathetic bedside manner
留給你那不長久的新女友吧
for your new, presumably temporary, girlfriend!
- 什麼? - 哦 得了...要滿足
- Excuse me? - Oh, come on... it can't be easy
上發條的淫妖兔的慾望可不容易啊
keepin' up with the Energizer SuccuBunny.
雖然戴森可以
Though Dyson could.
好吧 我覺得我們完事了
Okay... you know what? I think we're done.
不給我換點藥嗎
Any chance of a prescription refill?
- 出去! - 真的嗎?
- Out! - Really?
無情的醫生
Bloody physicians.
想像一下 假設什麼也沒問題
I mean, imagine sayin' that there's nothing wrong with it.
你聽過這麼扯的
I mean, have you ever heard anything so...
喂! 酒保! 我在跟你說話!
Hello! Barkeep! I'm talking to you!
- 還在說? - 難以置信!
- Still? - Unbelievable!
我在這兒掏心挖肺 你卻
Here I am, pouring out my heart to you and...
好吧 戴森 我可不是來娛樂的
Ok Dyson, I'm not here for my health.
你到底看不看這些文件?
You wanna look at these case files or not?
肯定看 再等等
Uh, absolutely. Just gimme a sec...
啊...問候你們呀
Ah... greetings.
- 閉嘴 伐克斯 - 什麼?
- Don't even start, Vex. - I beg your pardon?
- 我不會再給你買酒了 - 嘿  我很受傷誒
- I'm not buying you another drink. - Hey, I'm deeply offended.
- 很好 現在滾吧 - 嘿 你管不著我
- Good, now go away. - Hey, you don't own me.
好吧 聽著...
Okay, look...
你那悲慘遭遇我們已經聽得耳朵起繭了
we've been listening to your same sad story for days.
黑暗異族不想要我 光明異族受不了我
The Dark doesn't want me. The Light can't stand me.
我的朋友們...哦等等...
My friends... Oh, wait...
他沒有朋友 是吧?
he doesn't have any, does he?
- 伐克斯弱爆了 - 這是在侮辱我!
- Sucks to be Vex. - This is an outrage!
九號球 橫袋
Nine ball... side pocket.
那個妞怎麼回事?
What is it with that chick?
她不待見你而已
She's just not feeling the love.
- 但為什麼? -因為她覺得你是個殺人犯?
- But why? - Because she thinks you're a murderer?
但更重要的是 你最近在忙什麼?
But more importantly, what have you been up to?
什麼? 哦...
What? Oh...
- 又是莫瑞根? - 哦 小菜一碟
- The Morrigan again? - Oh, piece of cake.
別小看那個女人
Don't underestimate that woman.
迦樓羅被打敗之後 光明異族
After the Garuda meltdown, the Light
和黑暗異族決定握手言和
and the Dark have agreed to play nice.
不結盟表示無保護
Unaligned means unprotected.
但是你忘了...
Oh, but you are forgetting...
我有這個
I have this.
我自己的小小保險
My own little insurance policy.
我還是覺得你應該跟阿什談一下
I still think you should talk to The Ash.
你看起來得好好休息一整子
You look like you could use a break.
我猜肯吉也可以
And I'm guessing Kenzi could, too.
不好意思...
Pardonez moi...
- 他又怎麼了? - 我不知道
- What's his problem? - I have no idea.
你自找的 你懂得
You brought this on yourself, you know.
你就是這麼當阿什的? 嚴愛政策?
Is this how you roll now? Tough love?
是你把莫瑞根拷在床上 拍了她的不雅照
You handcuffed the Morrigan to her bed for a Kodak moment.
你確定這跟
You sure this has nothing
你的異種聯合國實驗沒關係?
to do with your Fae United Nations experiment?
光明異種和黑暗異種搭檔辦案? 搞毛?
A Light cop partnered with a Dark cop? Really?
正是這種憤世嫉俗
It's cynicism like that has kept our sides
阻礙了真正和平的建立
from building a genuine peace.
還有 你戴森跟誰搞在一起管你什麼事?
Also, why do you care who Dyson is paired with?
- 我沒有 - 我可不覺得
- I don't. - Didn't think so.
知道怎麼做可以幫你擺脫現狀嗎?
Know what might help your situation?
碰巧我準備好了對光明異族的宣言書
Just so happens I had a declaration to the Light all prepared...
我是不會因為恐懼而被迫選擇陣營的
I'm not gonna be pressured into choosing a side out of fear.
好吧 不能怪我想試試
Well, can't blame an Ash for tryin'.
聽著 別管我了 我自己能解決這堆麻煩
You know what? Forget it. I can handle the shitstorm,
只是肯吉自己在糾結而已
it's just that Kenzi is starting to feel the strain.
現在誰才在上演嚴愛戲碼?
Now who's dishing out tough love?
波 等一下...
Bo, hang on...
聽著 自從我們解決掉迦樓羅之後
Look, since we got all Garuda-fied,
我一直在整理保存的機密文檔
I've been doing some serious inventory of the archives.
結果?
And... ?
似乎有人偷走了我的正義之杖
Seems someone has grabbed my Staff of Righteousness.
是一根木製的權杖
The Staff is a piece of wood...
珍貴的儀式遺物...能力強大
a treasured ceremonial relic ... and very powerful.
據調查這權杖最近現在
Currently believed to be in the possession
在莫蒂默·法斯賓德的手上 卑鄙的典當商
of one Mortimer Fassbinder. Pawnbroker and sleazebag.
所以 如果我把權杖帶來給你...
So, if I bring you this Staff...
我也許會派一支特遣隊到你家附近
I could probably post a security detail near your place.
幫你留意莫瑞根的寵物
Keep an eye out for The Morrigan's pets.
- 我去哪裡找這個法斯賓德? - 別心急 看反面
- Where do I find this Fassbinder? - Hold up, Slick...
你必須瞭解一下這權杖的背景知識
There's something you should know about the Staff.
謝了 布魯斯!
Cheers, Bruce!
可愛的女士 今天是你的幸運日
Lovely lady, it is your lucky day.
你邁入門檻那刻我就可以殺了
I could have you killed just for crossing my threshold.
嘖嘖 冤冤相報何時了
Tut tut, bygones and all that...
請讓我深切表達我對黑暗異族和你的忠誠
A heartfelt expression of my loyalty to the Dark. And you.
被困的我依然勾人
I am beautiful in restraints.
刪除...
Delete...
- 還有什麼別的事嗎? - 哦 你不該高興才對嗎
- Was there something else? - Well, I thought you'd be pleased.
如果你真心想討好我
If you really wanted to please me you would have
你就該提著那小賤人的頭來見我
brought me that bitch's head on a platter.
但是... 但是我...
But... but, I...
但是最近你好像異種能力盡失?
But maybe your recent bout of impotence has spread to your spine?
算你走運 我同情心氾濫
Lucky for you, my pity outweighs my disgust.
我不會殺掉你的 至少不是今天
I won't have you killed. At least not today.
哦... 你太大度了
Oh... you're too kind.
我們都有自己的苦衷
We all have our cross to bear.
喝了它快滾吧
Now drink up and go.
下次我見到你...
The next time we meet...
你和波不是她死就是你亡 你自己選擇吧
...either Bo or you will be dead. The choice is yours.
- 嗨 - 哦 嗨
- Hey. - Oh, hey.
你在做什麼?
Whatcha doin'?
哦 只是做些醫生的實驗
Oh, you know, just some Doctor-y stuff.
你知道 我確實對你的工作很感興趣
You know, I am actually interested in your work.
你可以告訴我你在做什麼的
You can talk to me about whatever it is you do.
真的? 你想聽聽我最近著手的論文
Really? You want to hear about my latest monograph
關於與人類血液相比異種血液的
regarding the rhizome repellent gradient of Fae blood compared
排斥梯度
with human blood,
尤其是當其懸浮在等滲溶液中
especially when suspended in an isotonic solution?
- 或者我們可以去看部電影 - 好吧
- Or we could go to a movie. - Okay.
- 那是什麼? - 哦...
- What is that? - Oh...
- 正義之杖 - 什麼玩意?
- The Staff of Righteousness. - The who of what?
別問了 哦 也別碰
Don't ask. Oh, and don't touch.
那麼 我能摸什麼?
Well... what can I touch?
啊哈 真有趣
Haha, very funny.
你怎麼啦?
What's gotten into you?
怎麼說 本來還真沒啥目的
Well, you know, nothing just yet.
但是現在我想也許我們可以...
But I was kinda thinking maybe we could, um...
哦...
Oh...
哇 我以為我只是順路經過
wow... I think I just came by
看看我的手機是不是落在這裡
to see if I left my phone here.
嗯... 我不清楚 讓我們看看...
Hmm... I don't know. Let's look...
它不在這裡 天啊
Well, it's not in there. Gosh, you know,
也許你把它調到震動模式了
with any luck maybe you left it on "Vibrate".
我以為昨晚之後你會很疲倦
I thought you'd be too tired after last night.
疲倦? 我可是力爭金牌啊
Tired? I am going for the gold in the Succu-games.
好吧... 我不知道你怎麼了
Well... I don't know what's gotten into you,
但我不能阻礙
but far be it from me to
一個年輕運動員的奪金夢
stand in the way of a young athlete's dream.
- 呦 阿伐 - 隨你怎麼叫
- Yo, V-man. - Whatever.
聽上去好像某人情緒低落啊
Sounds like somebody woke up on the wrong side
換了個人似的 怎麼啦?
of the pull-out couch this morning. What's up?
- 是我的胳膊 - 又在討同情了?
- It's my arm. - Again with the pity parade?
聽著 你的翅膀折了 你不能飛了
Look, you got a busted wing, you can't fly.
你要像我們這些可悲的人類一樣活著了
You gotta walk around like the rest of us poor miserable humans.
歡迎來到肯吉的世界! 老兄!
Welcome to Kenzi-ville! Man!
現在你知道每天被一群超級英雄
Now you know what it's like to be surrounded
環繞左右的感覺了吧 別抱怨了 可憐蟲
by superheroes every day. Suck it up, Pathetico!
如果我是你 我會重新考慮在做社工
You know, if I were you, I'd re-consider a career in social work.
我們能不能
Can we just...
忽略你的異種身份哪怕十億分之一秒
...forget about your Fae-self for like a nanosecond,
來聊一聊真正重要的事情?
and talk about something that's really important?
我表示懷疑
Doubtful.
- 睫毛膏 - 我洗耳恭聽
- Mascara. - You have my attention.
老兄 你的睫毛美翻了!
Dude, your lashes are freakin' amazing!
是啊...刷睫毛的手法最重要 等等
Yeah... it's all in the brush technique. Wait...
我在達·芬奇那裡找到了些小竅門
I picked up a few tips from Da Vinci.
- 像達芬奇密碼一樣? - 對 現在那裡有個娘炮
- As in The Code? - Oh, yeah, now there was a queen for ya.
他就是戴維的跟屁蟲
He was all over David's ass like curry on chips.
- 你能幫我整理下結塊的睫毛嗎? - 哦別這樣
- Can you help me with my clumping? - Oh, please...
嗨 大傢伙
Hey, y'all.
嗨... 怎麼了?
Hey... Whazat?
長話短說 這就是個關於
The end of a long story, involving
諂媚的典當商和曖昧談判的故事
a greasy pawnbroker and some hardcore negotiating.
呃 別吵 我們在做正事呢
Uh, do you mind? We're working over here.
有人看見我的手機了嗎?
Anyone seen my phone?
你說手機? 怎麼 你的手機?
You say phone? What, your phone?
聽著 高抬貴臀讓我看看坐墊下面有沒有
Here, shift a cheek so I can look under the cushions...
沒有
Nothing...
- 往旁邊挪! - 你最後一次用它在哪裡?
- Scootch! - Where'd you last have it?
這就是問題關鍵... 我發誓我把它放在...
That's the thing... I coulda sworn that I left it...
Ipad Iphone什麼的電子產品
Yeah, iPads, iPhones electricity...
說實話 只是一時狂熱而已
it's all just a fad, really.
類似產品數不勝數 真理哦
The future's analog and all that. I'm tellin' ya.
我這麼刷對嗎?
Am I doing it right?
呃...
Uh...
嗯... 再往上一點...
Hmm... just a little bit up...
我 的 天
O.M.G.
你們在一起太有愛了
You guys are so cute together.
- 哈! - 呵...
- Ha! - Huh...
但願我也能有個一起化妝的夥伴
I wish I had a makeup buddy.
我本以為她可以成為朋友 可她壓根就不喜歡我
I thought she could be my friend, and she doesn't even like me.
- 誰? - 塔米辛!
- Who? - Tamsin!
她老刻薄了 對吧?
She is so mean girl, right?
我的意思是 就一個擁有實際人格的異種來說
I mean, buy an actual personality already.
你該不會是碰巧搜了我的行李箱
Did you happen to rifle through my duffel bag,
然後吞掉了那些老虎圖案的黃色藥片?
and scarf down a couple of yellow pills with tigers on 'em?
我要跟戴森談談
I'm gonna talk to Dyson.
順便說一下 這可以是私人秘密
and BTW?, It is "tres" private.
私密?
Private?
勞倫要怒火中燒了!
Lauren's pelt is gonna be steamed!
你跟那個醫生又是什麼恩怨?
What's it with you and the Doc?
我指 除了她對病人的態度
I mean, besides her terrible bedside manner
和她腦瓜比你靈的事實
and the fact that she's a damn sight cleverer than you.
還很卑鄙 她在監視波
Not to mention sneaky. She spy-banged Bo.
可戴森傷了波這麼多次
Dyson's drop-kicked Bo's heart ten times over,
而且他在的時候你還對他大吼大叫的
and you still howl when he comes 'round.
我...! 沒有!
I...! No!
聽著 你到底還要不要教我
Listen, are you gonna teach me
雙面防水防污刷睫毛法了?
the double pump smudge-proof technique or not?
我為你感到驕傲 過來...
I'm so proud of you. Come here...
好了 你要像這樣刷睫毛根部
Alright, you're gonna move it like this just at the ends.
你不要... 手抖...
You can't... like shake it...
我不喜歡你朋友
I do not like your friend.
她不是我朋友 她只是我的新搭檔
She's not my friend. She is my new partner.
她怎麼說的我?
What is she saying about me?
不管她怎麼說 那都不是真的
Because whatever it is, it's not true.
- 你喝高了? - 什麼? 你指酒?
- Have you been drinking? - What? Like, alcohol?
我倒希望如此
I wish.
- 你有假身份證嗎? - 什麼?
- Do you have fake ID? - What?
我們做吧
Let's do it.
我們去吧
Let's get faced!
好吧 你有點不對勁 我要去跟特裡克談談
Okay, you are cut off. I'm gonna talk to Trick.
哇 你真美
Wow, you're so beautiful.
抱歉...
I'm sorry...
我得走了...
I gotta go...
- 我認為戴森喜歡我 - 什麼?
- I think Dyson likes me. - Say what?
別告訴別人... 但我有吻他的衝動!
Don't tell anyone this... but I think I might kiss him!
瞳孔沒有擴張...
There's no pupil dilation...
沒有腦震盪
no concussion...
我困惑了
I'm stumped.
你的眼眸就像星星一樣閃亮
You have little specks in your eyes that look like stars.
當我多慮了 但是你
Call me crazy, but based on
在酒吧的狀態
your little display at the bar...
我是說 我知道你和戴森有過去
I mean, I do know that you and Dyson...
三號通道洩露! 三號通道洩露!
Spill on aisle 3! Spill on aisle 3!
嗷 嗷
Ow, ow...
來嘛! 我們去看電影吧
Come on! Let's go to a movie.
哇 火辣的美妞 你吻過女孩不?
Wow, you're really hot. Have you ever kissed a girl?
我需要你乖乖坐好 還得檢查你的心電圖 好嗎?
I need you to sit still to check your EKG, ok?
- 呲 - 波 別鬧!
- Bzzz! - Bo, stop!
現在我們已經交換了腦電波
We have now swapped brains.
嗨 我是勞倫醫生 我特無趣
Hi, I'm Dr. Lauren. I don't like to have any fun.
帶兩個皺眉圖案的布朗尼蛋糕 明天打電話找我吧
Take two frownie brownies and call me in the morning.
你這樣兒真嚇到我了
You're really starting to scare me.
好了 波 聽我說
Okay Bo... just listen to me...
波! 聽我說
Bo! Listen to me...
你最近有接觸過陌生的異種嗎
have you come in contact with any strange Fae lately...?
- 這太無聊了 - 波 拜託!
- This is so lame! - Bo! Please!
好吧
Okay, well...
倒是遇到一個揮著魔棒的惡男
there was this one gross guy with a magic stick...
嗨 塔米兒 塔辛 砰砰辛警官
Hey, Tammers. "T-sin". Officer "Slamsin"!
- 好吧 - 你這是在自娛自樂嗎?
- Okay... - Are you playin' with yourself?
這是誰拿啤酒把你給灌倒了?
Did somebody spike your brewski?
兄弟 這一刻終於發生了
Dude... this one time That totally happened.
我要扮肯吉 一個模子刻出來的有木有
I got to be Kenzi. Nailed it.
好吧 這要是是你想在我們辦案前就想讓我出局
Right... if you're trying to throw me off my game
這招還真管用了
before we get down, it's working.
- 你覺得波對我有好感嗎? - 我看著像管這種閒事的人麼
- Do you think Bo likes me? - Do I look like I care?
我想約她出去
I think I'm gonna ask her on a date.
好吧 你自便吧
Okay, well... knock yourself out.
於此同時 你要不就一起玩
In the meantime... you're either in the game...
- 要不就別擋道 - 你真是個壞傢伙
- or you are in my way... - You are so badass.
波和戴森排排坐樹上
Bo and Dyson sitting in a tree...!
噓!
Shhhhhh!
親親吻吻真親密
K-I-s-s-I-n-g!
哦 這場景太浪漫了! 但是 噓! 隔牆有耳
Oh, that would be so awesome! But, shhh! People are listening.
- 嗨 爺爺 這是啥? - 十七世紀
- Hey, Gramps, what's this? - Seventh century.
拜託 請把它放回我的書桌
Please, put it back in my study.
- 惡 她樣子好醜 - 把它放回去
- Ew, she's gross. - Just put it back.
把它放回去 能把車鑰匙給我嗎?
"Put it back." Can I have the car keys?
不行
No.
要是不給我車鑰匙 我就用法語數數
If I don't get the car keys, I'm gonna count to a hundred.
數到一百為止
In French .
- 老天 - 看到沒?
- Good grief... - See what I mean?
一
Un.
二!
Deux!
三
Trois...
你覺得她這症狀
You think this is being
像是因為阿什派她處理的任務而引起的嗎?
caused by the job that The Ash sent her on?
四
Quatre...
你說呢
You tell me.
四
Quatre...
會不會是正義之杖引起這樣的症狀?
Can the Staff of Righteousness have symptoms like these?
- 四! - 是五!
- Quatre...! - Cinq!
- 我的神 是五! - 抱歉 法國警官
- For the love of Aphrodite, it's cinq! - Sorry, French Police.
五
Cinq.
六
Six...
乍看之下 沒有記錄
At first glance, there's nothing in the lore
顯示這根權杖會引起這樣的症狀
that suggest the Staff is causing her symptoms.
但你也不能否認 這是很詭異的巧合
You have to admit, it's a pretty strange coincidence.
她找回權杖後 就成現在這個
She goes looking for the Staff and comes back like...
- 無憂無慮的傻妞 - 沒錯
- Pollyanna on mushrooms? - Exactly.
- 嗨 - 怎麼了?
- Hey... - What?
怎麼沒聽到數七?
Where's "Seven"?
波 快下來!
Bo, get down!
嘿! 讓我跳完! 別對我說教
Hey! Let me finish! Don't Kanye me.
- 你作弊! - 你能奈我何!
- You are a cheater! - Whatever!
你個騙子 詛咒你長痘痘
You're a cheater. And you're getting a zit.
波說的對 你個刻薄的女人!
Bo is right. You're mean!
不管是什麼引起的 這症狀會傳染
Whatever this is... it's contagious.
別用棕色了 黑色才能刷出新意
...you gotta forget about brown... black is always the new black.
- 你別老跟著我們 - 是啊 你又不是我們的老媽
- You can't ground us. - Yeah. You're not our Mom.
沒錯 我們才不要聽你的話
Yeah, we don't even have to listen to you.
所以 波把他倆都帶瘋了?
So... Bo shagged them both daft?
- 我們有麻煩了 - 更像是爛麻煩
- We have a situation. - More like a SHITuation.
你們像參觀參觀我的臥室嗎?
You guys wanna see my room?
- 額 當然 - 看誰跑得快!
- Uh... yeah! - Shotgun!
- 不! 不! - 別 等等! 等等!
- No! No! - No, wait! Wait!
有東西引起了這個症狀 更糟糕的是
Something's made them sick. And what's worse is the...
- 這是? - 一頭豬?
- Is that...? - A pig...?
他在尋找些什麼東西
He's looking for something...
或是什麼人! 波
Or someone! Bo...
肯吉 刀在哪兒? 你的工具箱也行?
Kenzi, where is there a knife? Or your trunk?
- 額 在樓上呢! - 好吧 那你的劍呢?
- Uh, upstairs! - Well, what about your sword??
- 在 樓上! - 好吧 肯吉 趕緊想辦法!
- Up... stairs! - Okay, well, Kenzi, think of something!
動腦筋神馬的不是一般都是你的事麼 醫生!
That's usually your thing, Doc!
這隻小肥豬就準備去市場掛售吧
This little piggy's about to go to market!
我們需要武器! 我們需要東西來防衛!
We need a weapon! We need something!
該死的
Bloody hell...
行了 豬豬 行了
That'll do, pig... that'll do.
你是怎麼
How did you...
我
I...
原來你才是匹黑馬
Aren't you the dark horse.
他死了
He's dead.
兄弟 我只是隨手抓了根棍子
Dudes, all I did was grab this stupid shillelagh
然後突然之間我就成了達斯·維達
and all of a sudden I'm Darth Vader.
- 讓我看看 - 說起這個
- Let me see that... - Yeah, about that...
這棍子貌似有點 粘在手上拿不下來了
the shaft is kinda... Fae-zy Glued to my hand.
是啊 我也有類似經歷
Yeah... That happened to me once.
苦不堪言
Painful.
"趕緊拿個武器"她如是說
"Grab a weapon," She said.
這看起來像是高能鍵
It seems to be an energy bond.
- 那就解開鍵連吶 - 做不到啊
- So un-bond it. - I can't.
這木頭和你手上的肉融為一體了
The wood is melded to your flesh.
世上最挫的手淫工具
Worst hand job ever.
哇 老兄! 拿刀作甚?
Whoa, Mack! The knife!?
不是啊 我電視上看到的 切木頭和番茄
No, I saw it on TV. It cuts right through wood.
輕而易舉
And tomatoes.
不是我的錯 棍子惹的禍
Not my bad. Stick bad.
還有 這音樂難聽死了!
Plus... your music sucks!
我買那碟是用來鄙視的
I bought that one ironically.
說實話 沒看得上眼的
All of them, actually...
- 額 這到底是啥? - 哦 看看這貨!
- Um, what the heck is this? - Oh! Look at that!
你聲音怎麼了?怎麼突然冒蘇格蘭口音
What is with your voice? It's all Scottish-y.
哦 好吧 你喜歡不?
Oh! Well, do you like it?
挫透了
It's lame.
- 不喜歡 喲 同志們! 我們遭攻擊了
- No. - Yo, peeps! We are under attack!
- 尖叫聲在哪裡 - 這下好了
- Big whoop. - Fascinating.
他們貌似連危機感都消失了
They seem to be immune to any sense of danger.
哦 真要命 嘿!
Oh for god sakes... Hey!
我們客廳還躺著只死豬呢
We have a dead man-pig in the living room,
我這還有根樹枝離不了手
I have a tree stuck to my mitt,
我可不想報名加入幼托俱樂部
and I did not sign up for the babysitter's club!
哦 戴森碰到我的胸了!
Oh, Dyson touched my boob!
這是個意外! 那是我胳膊肘干的!
That was an accident! It was with my elbow!
拜託!這不算!
Doesn't even count! Come on!
不是吧!
Seriously?
同志們 同志們 同志們! 我們點披薩吃吧!
Guys, guys, guys! Let's order pizza!
沒錯
Yes.
他們三個處於某種原因都被感染了
For some reason, only the 3 of them are infected.
我們要小心點
Let's not take any chances.
不要和他們有肢體接觸直到我找到真正病因
No physical contact until I know what we're dealing with.
- 明白了 - 雙層奶酪! 好耶!
- Got it. - Double cheese! Yeah!
雙層奶酪! 披薩!
Double cheese! PiZZA!
- 披薩! - 披薩!
- Pizza!!! - Pizza!
然後你們三個 乖乖呆著別亂跑
And you three, stay put.
快買披薩來!
Get the pizza!
這些武器你哪兒來的?
Where did you get these??
- 太屌了! - 給我一把
- It's fantastic! - Give it to me...
弱爆了
Totally lame...
哇 這還有一把! 你!放馬過來吧
Aww... There's another one! Come here, you!
我不明白的是
What I don't understand
要是異種才是感染對像
is that if this disease only targets Fae...
那為什麼伐克斯沒事呢?
Why isn't Vex infected?
怎麼說 也許是我超級逼真的妝容
Well, perhaps my superior genetic makeup
免疫了外界的侵害
has rendered me immune to embarrassing afflictions.
- 那是啥? - 什麼?
- What is that? - What?
你耳後有奇怪的膿包
You have a strange pustule behind your ear
我上次給你檢查的時候還沒有呢
that wasn't there when I examined you last.
膿包 惡
Pustule... Ew.
惡 噁心!
Ugh... Ugh! UGH!
噁心死人了
Ewww with a double side of hurl.
- 這是什麼? - 像是什麼留下的繭
- What is it?? - It's what's left of a cocoon.
看來你被用作孵卵器了
You've been used as an incubator.
- 被什麼當做孵卵器? - 我的猜測
- By what? - My guess?
- 寄生蟲 - 什麼? 我不乾淨?
- A parasite. - What? I'm unclean?!
放輕鬆 已經不在你體內了
Relax... it isn't in you anymore.
但是你哪兒招來的這寄身蟲呢?
But where could you have picked this up?
你最近有很陌生異種待一起麼?
Have you been with any strange Fae lately?
呃 他媽的賤人!
Ugh... damn bitch!
- 那是怎麼了? - 那是怎麼了?
- What's that? - What's that?
哦 沒事 額
Oh, nothing, uh...
這事搞得我好受傷 額
I was just saying how devastated I was about all this, uh...
聽著 我這就去找特裡克幫忙 好不?
Listen, I'm gonna get some help from Trick. Alright?
我會想辦法補救的 好不?
I'm gonna make things right. Alright?
你他媽對我做了什麼?
What the hell did you do to me!?
拿你當傳播寄生蟲的利器了
Used you to spread a parasite.
- 哪種變態寄生蟲 - 吸元寄生的那種
- What kind of bloody parasite!? - The parasitic kind.
靠吸取被害者對他人好感的荷爾蒙為生
Zaps its victims with nymphoid hormones.
把他們變成自戀頑童無法控制異種能力
Turns them into self-obsessed brats too young for Fae powers.
所以 他們易受攻擊?
So, they're completely vulnerable to attack?
沒錯
Precisely.
那那些豬呢? 你派來的?
But what about the "Other white meat"? Relatives of yours?
感染源會發出刺激性荷爾蒙
The infected emit a pungent pheromone that attracts
吸引那些骯髒的下等異種來殺戮
a nasty breed of UnderFae in for the kill.
是啊 幸好肯吉用魔法小木棍把那小豬扭扭
Yeah, well, luckily Kenzi pounded little Piggly Wiggly
揍成了下等異種燻肉
into UnderFae bacon with her magic shillelagh.
- 那個賤女淫妖呢? - 還活蹦亂跳的呢
- And the Succubitch? - Still alive and singing.
還有兩個悲劇帝 戴森和他的新搭檔
Along with the other Twi-hards. Dyson and his new partner.
哦!事情真是越來越有趣了
Oh! Now this is getting interesting.
我最愛的三個人 被困在了一個地方
Three of my favorite people, trapped in one place...
無法自衛
with no way to defend themselves.
人類小女孩還拿著阿什的魔棒
And she's got The Ash's play stick.
想證明你對黑暗異族的忠誠嗎?
You want to prove your loyalty to the Dark?
把那腦殘三人組結果了吧
Finish off the teen trio,
然後把正義之杖帶回來給我
and bring me the Staff of Righteousness.
要是我做到了?
And if I do?
我可以保證幫你找幾個 初級崗位
I'm sure I could find some... entry level position...
做夢! 我要名至實歸 百萬現金
No! I want all titles restored ... A million in cash
還有我要拿回我的俱樂部
and my club. I want it back.
這才是我認識的伐克斯
There's the Vex I remember.
"趕緊拿個武器"她如是說
"Grab a weapon", she said...
我已經解釋好多次了 肯吉 我不知道會這樣!
For the hundredth time, Kenzi, I didn't know!
知會媒體同胞 居然有完美醫生不知道的事情!
Alert the media, there is something Doctor Flawless doesn't know!
那是緊要關頭 肯吉
This is hardly the time, Kenzi.
當然不是 因為要是緊要關頭肯定早已一片狼藉
Course it isn't... 'Cause that would be "Messy"!
你不能來一次 一次也行 你能試著
Do you think just once! Maybe just once, you could try to be...
- 試著幹嘛? - 有所幫助!
- What? What?? - Helpful!
- 你說什麼? - 沒錯!
- Excuse me? - Sure!
因為大家都盡其所能
Because everybody else does!
你卻混混度日 沒工作 沒計劃 成天飲酒作樂
You just bounce through life, no job, no plan, from one beer
每個人都把你捧手心裡 難道不是?
to the next and still, everybody dotes on you, don't they?
他們寵誰礙著你什麼事了?
What do you care where they dote?
- 當我沒說 - 是啊 你這算什麼
- Just forget about it... - Yeah... what is that?!
你為什麼老用你那正常成長的經歷
Why are you always rolling your eyes at me,
和醫學學位翻白眼給我看
with your normal upbringing and your medical degree.
我過的是怎樣的生活你毫不知情 肯吉
You don't know anything about my life, Kenzi!
我知道你看不起我
I know you think you're too good for me...
不 我真沒有 是你覺得我配不上波
No, I don't actually! You think that I'm not good enough for Bo!
- 她是我閨蜜 - 可我也愛她
- She's my best friend. - And I love her.
我知道 我知道
I know! I know.
你確定我們沒被感染?
Are you sure we're not infected?
姆
Mmmm...
沒 我們只是
No. We're just...
犯傻
...stupid.
好吧 我還是喜歡"情緒化"一詞
Well, I prefer... ..."emotional".
不棄前嫌?
Moving on?
- 一起宰豬? - 好
- Killer Pig? - Yeah...
好的
Yep, okay...
我不敢相信我居然以為你不待見我
I can't believe I ever thought you didn't like me.
我不認為我能喜歡你
I don't think I was supposed to like you.
為什麼?你這是什麼意思?
Why? What do you mean?
我是瓦爾基裡
I'm a Valkyrie.
- 好像是 - 哇
- I think. - Wow...
真的?
Really?
- 瓦爾基裡是什麼? - 我不知道
- What's a Valkyrie? - I don't know.
但是 有時當我有所愛
But... sometimes when I like people,
我卻不得不放手
I have to make them go away.
- 你這是什麼意思? - 你會保守秘密嗎?
- What are you talking about? - Can you keep a secret?
至死不渝
Till I die.
姆
Um...
- 不 我不能說的 - 別 等等 等等!
- No, I'm not supposed to. - No, wait! Wait!
我有個主意 這樣
I have an idea! Okay...
我們把自己最黑暗 隱藏最深的秘密以詩的形式
Let's write down our deepest, darkest secrets...
寫下來
...in poetry.
酷!
Cool!
但要真的像首詩啊 要押韻的那種
But like real poetry. The kind that rhymes.
你真是個很好的人
You're really awesome.
不 你才是
No. You're really awesome.
額
Um...
哦 哦!
Oh, oh!
看到那豬臉了嗎?
See its snout?
它的遺傳結構與豬相似
It's similar in genetic makeup to the pig.
他以氣味捕食獵物 他知道我們之中
It was scenting out its prey, it knew which of us
誰感染了寄生蟲
was infected with the parasite.
塊菌豬威武霸氣
Hurray for the Truffle Pig.
這種生物群居為生
These creatures travel in packs.
當他們的兄弟沒有回去
When their buddy doesn't return...
他們就群攻?
They'll all go hog wild?
我們的魔法棒也不夠救咱們的
Not even my wonder whacker may be enough to save us.
所以我們需要波和其他人恢復正常
That's why we need Bo and the others back to normal.
根據我從伐克斯耳後的繭中提取的分泌物
Based on the secretions that I pulled from the cocoon
我可以湊出個寄生蟲的抗生素
from Vex, I think I can cobble together an anti-toxin
- 但我需要時間 - 也許還要個實驗室
- for the parasite. But I need time. - And a lab, maybe?
好吧 這倒不必 我工具箱裡有些基本配備
Well, not necessarily. I've got a few basic supplies in my kit.
但我需要你幫我去湊齊幾味配料
But I need you to gather up some ingredients.
呃 發酵粉 醋 薑黃
Uh, baking powder, vinegar, turmeric...
好 好 好的
Yeah, yeah, okay...
好了 說吧
Alright, go...
還有 大蒜 發膠和潤滑油
Also, garlic, hairspray, and lubricating oil.
加工的還是散裝的?
Flavoured or bulk?
至於我 我要去樓上採樣
As for me... I'm going upstairs to take a swab.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
醫生 你單槍匹馬的去了? 不帶個後援?
Doc, you goin' in solo? Without backup?
- 我能搞定 - 你的固執和專橫真是半斤八兩
- I think I can do this. - You're as stubborn as you are bossy.
祝你成功
Godspeed.
好吧!
Okay!
- 發生什麼事了? - 不想說這個
- What happened? - I don't want to talk about it.
但是 我拿到樣本了
But... I got it.
的確
Sure did.
哇
Wow...
- 做的不錯 - 是啊 我還會幹其他事
- Nice job. - Yeah, I did something else too...
我還在外面裝了一個預警系統 小鬼當家范兒
I set up an early warning system outside, Home Alone style.
很好 會有幫助的
Good. That'll help.
好了
Okay...
你肯定畢業於哪個瘋人醫學院
You must've gone to some crazy-ass medical school.
耶魯教會了我化學和生理學
Yale taught me chemistry and physiology.
但是這東西只是經驗和運氣
But this kind of stuff is just experience and luck
是我實地經驗琢磨出來的
and whatever I figured out in the field.
- 實地說的是 - 阿富汗
- "Field" Meaning... - Afghanistan.
要命 姐們
Shit, dude...
- 呆了多長時間 - 長到都忘記了
- How long? - Long enough.
- 你以前怎麼不曾提起? - 你又沒問
- Why didn't you ever say so? - You never asked.
你在聽戴森尿尿
You're listening to Dyson take a whiz.
我才沒有
I am not.
你讀了我的詩沒? 寫的很爛 是吧?
Did you read my poem? It was stupid, right?
沒 我喜歡 很喜歡
No, I liked it. A lot.
在某種程度上 你寫的很美
Yours was really beautiful... in a way.
但是這故事真的 真的很悲傷
But it was... really, really sad.
我真希望能做些什麼可以幫到你
I wish there was something I could do to help you.
你幫不了我的
You can't help me.
沒人幫得了我
Nobody can.
這是我們的秘密?
Our secret?
我發誓
Cross my heart.
請把我變成異妖吧
Make mine a Fae-cuccino, please...
我剛剛過濾了雜質 老天 我希望
I'm just straining any impurities. God, I hope...
警報響起!
Perimeter breach!
- 額 我們有伴了 - 有多少?
- Uh... we've got company! - How many?
只有 額 不是 還有一個
There's just... Uh, no, there's another one...
- 呃 藥還沒做好 - 哦 老天
- Ugh, it's not ready! - Oh, God...
三頭小豬駕到! 這回可是人為哦
The 3 little piggies are back! And this time, it's personal.
- 伐克斯! 老兄 你這是在幹嘛?
- Vex! - Dude, what are you doing?
我要回家了
I'm going home.
- 你這虛偽的混蛋 - 噢
- You slimy sonuvabitch! - Ooooh!
這話真是傷我心啊!
Your words are like tiny little daggers in my heart!
我那麼相信你!
I trusted you!
那麼 把淘氣小淫妖交出來 讓我們早點打道回府!
Yeah, well, just give us the rugrats so we can all go home!
休想!
Not on your miserable life!
杜蘭杜蘭樂隊的歌?
Duran Duran?
波!救命!
Bo! Help!
好像是肯吉在叫你誒!
That sounds like Kenzi!
我飢餓如狼
"...I'm hungry like the wolf!"
波?!
Bo?!
- 把聲音調大點 塔米! - 好
- Crank it, Tammy! - Okay!
解毒劑準備完畢!
The antidote's ready!
- 我得上樓一趟 - 有多遠跑多遠 醫生!
- I need to get upstairs... - Go long and wide, Doc!
我掩護你!
I got you covered!
你沒事嗎?
Are you gonna be okay??
當然! 還挺有趣
Sure! This is kinda fun.
好吧 我設法別胡思亂想
Okay... Way to not overthink it.
嗨 小閃妞
Hey... Twinkle toes...
你的權杖我也要了
I'll be havin' that wee Staff of yours.
靠近點 我遞給你
Come closer. Let me give it you.
哦 我太高興了 看看我找到了什麼
Oh, I'd be delighted. Look what I found.
這和我以前
This isn't really like...
玩過的轉瓶遊戲大不一樣啊
any Spin The Bottle game I ever played.
- 哦 規則更新了 - 你確定?
- Oh, it's new rules. - Are you sure?
確定 我不知在哪兒 看過 輪到你了
Absolutely, I read it... somewhere. It's your turn.
- 我得吻你 - 好吧
- I gotta kiss you. - Okay.
- 天 你到底是誰? - 姐們 那是你的關係
- Man... what are you? - Dude... that was all you.
你們這是在玩轉瓶遊戲?
Are you playing Spin The Bottle?
爽斃了
That was so dope.
- 我們再來 - 好的
- Let's do that again. - Okay.
好吧 還是別了
Yeah, let's not...
喔
Ow!!!
- 嘿 我們的披薩呢? - 不會有披薩了
- Hey, where's our pizza? - There's no pizza coming.
過來啊 你個小
Come here, you little...
啊哈
Ahh...
我覺得你要說的應該是傻瓜一詞
I believe "Wanker" Is the word that you're looking for.
你個卑鄙的叛徒
A dirty traitor!
想想我還和你共享了
And to think I shared my
我的限量版紫精靈閃粉
limited edition purple-pixie glitter with you!
哇 你以為共享化妝品就讓我們成朋友了?
Aw, you think sharing makeup makes us friends?
別這樣 你能自己做主
Don't do this... I thought you were your own man.
我的確是自己的主宰啊 而且我剛好有把斧頭
I am my own man! And I happen to have an axe.
但是你不是為了自己才幹這事的
But you're not doing this for you.
你這麼做是為了那個賤女人
You're doing it for that stupid bitch!
做什麼也比這有格調
Anything is better than this!
我是說 看看我! 我睡沙發!
I mean, look at me! I'm sleeping on a couch!
人們都當面嘲笑我!
People are laughing at me to my face!
你不能相信莫瑞根
You can't believe that The Morrigan's
她不會滿心歡喜的歡迎你
just gonna welcome you back with open arms!
聽著 親愛的 明顯你也看過那本
Listen, luv, you've obviously read the book
人質談判第一章第一篇 所以我們能跳頁麼
on "Hostage Negotiation 101"... Can we just skip
說說我活成這樣哪裡好了
to the bit where you tell me I'm better than this?
- 這樣的你好 - 要是不好呢
- You are. - What if I'm not?
你失去了異種能力
Losing your powers was the
對你來說是最好的事情
best thing that could have happened to you.
我感覺我終於看到了真正的伐克斯
I feel like I've finally met the real Vex!
他是真正的藝術家! 他溫文爾雅!
He's a true artist. He's a gentle soul!
而且他不會被輕易愚弄 莫瑞根也不行
And he will not be trifled with. Not even by her!
他已經受夠了
He's done with that!
伐克斯 拜託!
Vex... please!
哦 肯吉
Oh, Kenzi...
我在年邁之時變溫柔了
I'm getting soft in my old age.
明智的選擇
Good choice...
Good choice!!!
沒事了
It's all right...
她來了
She's coming...
是時候老娘虐豬做燻肉了
Time for Mama to bring home the bacon.
- 哦 - 哦!
- Oh... - Oh!
我覺得被美人揍
I don't think I'd mind getting my ass kicked
- 我一定也不介意 - 可是很疼的
- by someone that hot. - That had to hurt.
惡
Ugh...
- 啊哈! - 哦 老天!
- Ah! - Oh! God!
還有一個 還有一個 還有一個!
One to go, one to go, one one one to go!
還有兩個 不 那有兩個!
And that's two! No, that's two!
波最棒!
Bo for the gold!
呃 結局皆大歡喜 是吧?
Ahem... Uh, all's well that ends well, yeah?
無惡意?
No hard feelings?
喔
Ow!
妞 你還真有一手 真話
Girl, you got you some gaaame. True.
加油 波
Come on, Bo...
發生了啥事 完全不記得了
The whole thing's... blank.
頭暈暈的 就像
But fuzzy, like...
的確發生了什麼 但是不記得了?
...like there's something there, but why can't I remember?
因為你本該忘記
Because you're not supposed to.
我們還是別糾結的好
We're probably better off this way.
是啊 注意不錯 塔米
Yeah, good call, Tammy.
- 我是說 塔米辛 - 好吧
- I mean, Tamsin. - Okay!
聽著 我就知道最近這破事
Look, all I know is that this latest crapfest
害我又多了幾份異種報告要寫
just caused a whole mess of Fae paperwork.
所以 謝謝你毀了我的週末 還有再見
So, thank you for destroying my weekend, and goodbye.
好吧 這姑娘一點都不幽默
Well, that girl is just no fun at all.
姆
Hmm...
執正義之杖之人
The one who touches the Staff of Righteousness
必須行使高尚之舉
shall take up the noble cause,
接受山林仙子寧芙的神聖斗篷
accept the sacred mantle of Ruler of Forest Nymphs
繼承叢林精神 發誓至始至終
and Wood Sprites, and fight for truth and justice
只為正義和真理而戰
throughout the land to the end of their natural days.
這是在玩我吧
You're kidding me.
你繼承了一個重大的責任
This is a huge responsibility you've taken on.
我就是信手拈來了個棍子!
I just picked up a frikkin' stick!
這就是傳說中命運 今天你還是你 明天
That's how destiny works. One day you're you, and the next day...
我就成了超級英雄
I'm a superhero.
好處
Pro...
我看起來永遠很屌
I could be awesome, forever.
- 沒錯 - 好吧 壞處
- Yup. - Okay... Con...
我得開始學習慣用左手
I would have to learn how to do everything
我是說幹啥都得左手
with my left hand and I mean everything.
好吧 作為最後 有個免除條款
Well... as a last, desperate resort there is an escape clause.
選了 趕緊告訴我怎麼脫離這棍子
Sold. Show me the eject button.
好吧
Very well.
閉上眼然後跟我念 不准偷瞄
Close your eyes and say the words... No peeking.
我拒絕
"I decline".
我 拒絕
I... decline.
就這麼簡單?
It was that easy?
你怎麼不早說?
Why didn't you just say so?
幹嘛? 血聖就不能找樂子麼?
What? A Blood King can't have a little fun?
你的室內裝潢師水平真不咋地
I don't think much of your interior decorator...
這只是還在裝修中
It's a work in progress.
和你一樣
Much like yourself.
別轉移話題 這事還沒完
Don't change the subject. You're not off the hook yet.
哦 看看你 瞬間老成相的阿什
Oh! Look at you. All grown up. "The Ash."
你有印新商務名片麼
Did you get the new business cards,
也許買了車辦了自選車牌
yet? Maybe a little vanity plate?
- 當爹的好光榮 - 你違反了異種法律
- Daddy must be so proud. - You violated Fae law.
哦 就逗逗淫妖這點小事麼?
Oh, by having a little fun with SuccuBo?
你招搖過市攻擊光明異族
You executed a blatant attack on the Light.
哦 拜託 啥時候大家都這麼神經過敏了?
Oh, come on now. When did everyone get so uptight?
我仍記得當年
I remember the good old days.
小搶小鬧
A little raping, a little pillaging,
古怪的"附帶損壞"
the odd "Collateral damage"...
然後再給自己辦個派對
and then you'd have yourself a party.
現在幹嘛都是規則 規則
Now it's all rules, rules, rules.
你的行為會破壞新的和平計劃
Your actions may have jeopardized the new peace plan.
怕你忘記 提醒你一下 這計劃
A plan, in case you've forgotten,
是由異種長老們決議通過的
that was endorsed by the Fae Elders themselves.
我能說什麼?
What can I say?
除了 我錯了
Except, mea culpa.
我就是想為生活添點情趣
I was just trying to spice things up a little bit.
我做了三十年的警察了
I was a cop for thirty years.
學會一件事 屁話臭不可聞
One thing I learned... bullshit stinks.
女士 你臭氣熏天了
And lady, you reek.
你要是再敢耍花招
You ever pull a stunt like this again,
我會親自宰了你
I will personally rip off
讓你好看
your head and shove it up your lily white ass.
這次緊張局面緩和相當重要
This detente is important to be screwed up
不能被瑣碎的小爭執給破壞了
by some petty feud.
聽清楚了沒?
Am I clear?
明白了
Crystal.
嗨 兄弟 我們剛從伐克斯缺席的嘉年華上回來
Hey man, we are just one Vex short of a real fiesta.
你要去哪兒?
Where you goin'?
還不知道
I don't know yet.
我去泡點茶
Why don't I go make some tea.
伐克斯親 嗨 拜託 我們都不計前嫌了
Vexster... hey! Come on, all is forgiven.
不能 肯吉
But it shouldn't be, Kenz.
我不能住這兒了 在我做了這樣的事之後
I can't stay here. Not after what I've done.
老兄 你救了我的命
Dude, you saved my life...
那只是那豬剛好移到了左邊
Or that pig shifted to the left at just the right moment.
才不是
That is not true.
不是 對吧
Is it??
你懂得
You know...
如果我翻過我的歷史 你就會知道我是個賭徒
if you'd looked at my history you'd know I was a betting man.
我要花點時間自舔傷口 你知道嗎?
I'm going to take some time to reflect, you know?
重啟系統 我猜醫生說得對!
Reset the system. I guess the Doctor was right!
見鬼的人類
Bloody humans...
- 你這是要去西藏? - 印度 路經維加斯
- You thinkin' maybe Tibet? - India, via Vegas.
你懂得 整個美食 祈禱 催眠之旅
You know, the whole Eat, Pray, Mesmer tour.
是啊 我會回來的
Yeah... well... I'll be back.
全副武裝 準備就緒
Fully armed and ready to rock.
那我什麼時候才能再見你?
How do I know I'll ever see you again?
不會是你黑檀木手柄豬鬃胭脂刷吧?
Not your ebony handled bison bristle blush brush?
呃
Ugh!
你要是搞壞了 我非殺了你不可
You break that brush and I'll kill ya.
嗷
Ow!
來世再見 也許
Catch you in another lifetime! Maybe...
我會想念那混蛋的
I'm gonna miss that a-hole...
我知道
I know.
- 噢 - 來吃
- Ow... - Here...